### DREW T. BROOKSBANK

2553 13<sup>th</sup> Avenue East ● North Saint Paul, MN 55109 ● DrewBrooksbank@gmail.com ● (651) 246-5267

#### SUMMARY

Professional with over 10 years of administrative experience. Unique combination of experience in Medical, Real Estate, Financial, Manufacturing, and Food Safety industries, demonstrated trust and responsibility to handle multiple tasks using expertise, knowledge, and experience in the administrative field. Experience gained in fast-paced environments while demonstrating a strong sense of urgency necessary for quickly troubleshooting and resolving critical issues with little to no supervision.

### **HIGHLIGHTS**

Punctual Results-oriented Organizational skills Client confidentiality
Quick learner Customer service Communication skills Creative thinker
Project management Mechanically inclined Time Management Reliable
Self-motivated Team player Troubleshooting

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# National Seating & Mobility, Inc., Maplewood, MN (Jamary 2018 – April 2018) Wheelchair Technician

- Assembled power and manual seating and mobility equipment in a timely manner
  - o . Made necessary equipment modifications to prepare goods for delivery to the patient.
- Responded to service calls and made repairs as needed in the office and in the field.
- Delivered equipment as directed by the Branch Manager.
- Assisted Rehab Technology Specialists with fitting, adjustment and equipment modification to ensure the best possible product for the patient.
- Responsible for all shipping and receiving duties related to daily operations.
  - Ensured timely receipt through tracking of purchase orders and maintains communication with vendors on orders received with damaged or missing goods.
- Attended seating clinics with the Rehab Technology Specialist as necessary to assist with evaluations, modifications, and deliveries.
- Disinfected loaner and demo wheelchairs to industry standards as they were returned to the shop.
- Provided inventory control for all special orders and stock items in the office.
- Maintained shop area in a neat and organized manner to ensure proper care of equipment.
  - o Assisted with quarterly physical count of inventory goods.
- Assisted in the timely completion of work orders, which involved research of components, calculation and extension of equipment price and preparation of quotes for patients, referral sources and insurance companies.
- Maintained Automobile Log on company vehicles.
  - o Ensured Branch Manager is informed of needed repairs and maintenance.
  - Obtained estimates for said repairs and schedules needed work.

## Lowe's Companies, Inc., Oak Park Heights, MN (July 2016 – January 2018) Facility Service Associate

- Executed superior customer service. Greet and acknowledge all customers in a friendly, professional manner and provide quick, responsive customer service.
- Greatly improved the cleanliness and general maintenance of the facility inside and out.
- Kept entrance/exit areas free of stray merchandise an! d debris. Performing basic preventative maintenance on store equipment.
- Performed repairs to facility and equipment as needed and escalated to outside vendors when deemed necessary.
- Maintained inventory of commonly used items for the building such as cleaning supplies, toilet paper, paper towels, and shipping/receiving items.
- Emptied all garbage container and dispose of properly.
- Touched up paint and swept floors as needed.
- Complied with all policies and procedures.

## Lowe's Companies, Inc., Oak Park Heights, MN (April 2016 – July 2016)

### Customer Service Associate- Outdoor Lawn and Garden

- Responsible for assisting customers with all of their shopping needs including assisting customers in the selection, demonstration, preparation, and loading of merchandise.
- Responded to customer inquiries throughout their shopping experience.

## 3M-Package Engineering Division, Maplewood, MN (April 2015 – September 2015)

Packaging Analyst (Contract position through Manpower Staffing)

- Maintained accurate and up-to-date packaging information in 3M proprietary software,
- Worked closely with other Packaging Analysts, Packaging Engineers, and managers to determine the best course for corrective actions.
- Maintained and prioritized a list of packaging issues for evaluation.
- Monitored, assessed and managed the effectiveness of implemented changes.

# HomeServices of America, a Berkshire Hathaway Affiliate, Minneapolis, MN (March 2014 – March 2015)

### Corporate Legal Assistant

- Provided executive level administrative support to the Senior Vice President/General Counsel, Associate General Counsel, and general support to three Corporate Counsel Attorneys, and two Paralegals.
- Demonstrated ability to research, process and present information.
- Organized and maintained correspondence, legal and data files, and multiple email accounts.
- Frequently made travel arrangements and managed itineraries for Senior Vice President, Associate General Counsel, and Corporate Counsel.
- Prepared weekly, monthly, and quarterly reports to be sent to parent company.
- Answered incoming calls and managed email inbox for Senior Vice President.
- Prepared weekly and monthly, and quarterly meeting agendas, and transcribed meeting minutes.
- Preformed data-entry as needed.
- Maintained calendars and schedules for Senior Vice President and Associate General Counsel.
- Processed invoices and payments and communicated with vendors.
- Maintained and updated legal department web portal.
- Demonstrated effective analytical, problem-solving and decision-making skills.

### US Bank, Minneapolis, MN (August 2005 – January 2014)

### Administrative Assistant

- Awarded quarterly "Bravo Award" for "exceptional performance and significant contribution to the achievement of business initiatives, goals, and objectives".
- Provided executive level administrative support to the Business General Manager demonstrating ability to improvise, improve procedures, and meet demanding deadlines.
- Worked as acting Paralegal for eight months while a replacement was found; was the central
  point of contact for all customer contracts while maintaining consistent contract versions for
  distribution to Sales Team.
- Provided administrative support to 19 direct reports of the Business General Manager and 140
  employees as needed.
- Prepared and updated tracking reports for division projects.
- Coordinated cubicle and floor moves for 80 employees; including network jack and phone jack reconfiguration, workstation and telephone location reassignment; articulated move procedures, requirements, and schedule to all employees involved.
- Established and maintained legal contracts filing system.
- Coordinated and planned meetings for management as needed.
- Handled confidential and sensitive information in a professional manner.
- Worked with managers and staff to create 300+ shared Standard Operating Procedure documents; directed staff on the transfer of the documents onto web-based Microsoft SharePoint platform.
- Planned and coordinated off-site business events including an annual conference and employee summer picnic.
- Assisted Contracts team on daily basis by entering 30+ newly approved contracts into the database.
- Served as department United Way coordinator for the annual fund drive.

### 3M-Automotive Division, Stillwater, MN (May 2005 – July 2005)

Administrative Coordinator (Temporary position through Volt Services)

- Processed incoming orders using AIM and Oman (3M proprietary order management software.)
- Collaborated with Shipping and Distribution departments to ensure order accuracy and timeliness.
- Worked quickly to process expedited orders and ensure they were ready for prompt freight pickup.

### Ecolab, St. Paul, MN (November 2004 – March 2005)

Administrative Assistant (Temporary position through Kelly Services)

- Coordinated daily meetings and made travel arrangements for Director of Operations and Strategic Alliances.
- Produced high-quality spreadsheets and documents using Microsoft Excel and Word,
- Performed secretarial, confidential and administrative assignments.
- Website Administrator for Garland Project providing daily updates to project website.

#### **EDUCATION**

**St. John's University**, Collegeville, MN Bachelor of Arts Degree Double major in Business Management and Art Administration